NexusFont

NexusFont is a font manager for Windows. If you have many fonts and you need to choose fonts you want, NexusFont is here for you.
You can compare many fonts at once. And there are useful functions to manage font files.


Main features: 

Supported Font Types:
- TrueType, TrueType Collection, OpenType, Adobe Type1
- view installed fonts, fonts in folders (not installed). 

Install/Uninstall fonts: 
- install fonts into system or uninstall fonts from system. 

Find Duplicate Fonts: 
- find duplicate fonts in folders and delete unnecessary font files. 

Print:
- print font list with user defined sample text 

Export as Image:
- export font list as an image with user defined sample text 

AntiAliasing:
- supports antialiasing for designers 

Rename:
- Rename many font files with their font name at once

Copy/Move/Delete:
- Basic file operations for managing font files

Favorite Fonts:
- manages fonts by favorite groups 

Unicode Support:
- Can be run on any language OS. Sample text, font file name or font name can be in any language.

Multi-language UI:
- Any language UI can be used with a translated language file.

Tags:
- Manages fonts with tags

Portable:
- NexusFont can be run in USB memory with font files in it. Even the drive letter is changed, all library information will be maintained.


System Requirement: Windows XP or above

License: Freeware

Designed and developed by xiles

===========================
JungHoon Noh (aka: xiles)
xiles@xiles.net
http://xiles.net
===========================
